

Beata Greń-Onderko beongren@gmail.com (+44) 7448 245462 d.o.b.: 31st August 1963 Polish full driving license CRB on demand

# Beata Greń-Onderko

### Weekend Cook

Career Profile I am a committed, hard working person who wants to make use of her abilites to cook good, healthy and natural food. I was always passionate about how diet influences human health, and I am still up to date with the newest dietary recomendations.

Key experience I regularly cook meal for an older lady, and sometimes help with health care. These meals are always made with very fresh ingredients. She particularly likes the soups that I make. I work in Westabank care home as a cook and my duties include cooking for at least 40 residents.

- hands-on experience of preparing food for large number of people
- good understanding of foods and nutrition suited to older people and basic hygiene good practice
- good knowledge of vegetarian dishes
- a good team worker
- a caring attitude to older people
- reliability and punctuality
- an awarness of costs in food preparation and interest in cuisine from different countries
- a willigness to learn and undertake an further training necessary to do a good job.
- an ability to learn quickly

# Work experience

20th October 2016- ...

Weekend Cook in Westbank Care Home

- Cooking for more than 40 residents
- Preparing breakfast, lunch, dinner, desserts, birthday cakes
- Works alone or with a help of the kitchen assistant
- Approximately 24 hours per week

17th May 2016 - October 2016

Sales assistant in Euro Garages (Ross-On-Wye) FULL TIME

8th May 2016 - ...

Cleaner (PART TIME) at Parkfields Country House. Duties: keeping all areas of Parkfields Country house clean and tidy, sorting laundry, dusting, polishing, sweeping.

#### September 2015-April 2016

Au pair for two children : girl 22 months, girl 4.5 years old in Ross-on-Wye, UK

#### October 1986-June 1987

Afternoon babysitting in family orphanage: girl(8 years old); boy (8 years old); girl aged 12 with schizophrenia;

#### 1988-89

24h/7 babysitting of 9-month old baby girl;

#### July 1990-August 1991

Au pair in Ventabren, France; 2 children: boy aged 1,5 and boy aged 3 as well as taking care of the house (cleaning, cooking, laundry etc.)

## Training and Courses

#### 03rd October 1985 -19th May 1986

First aid course at Polish Red Cross at PRC Wrocław

#### August 1986

One month <u>language scholarship</u> founded by French Embassy at University of Grenoble, France

#### 02nd March 2009-30th June 2009

Training in Social Integration Center (Centrum Integracji Społecznej) in Wrocław. Aim: schooling in licensing and running social cooperative (446 hours)

#### 10th September 2009-19th December 2009

English language course at Pre-Intermediate level in Yellow Language Center Sp. z.o.o (64 hours)

#### January - August 2010

Participation in "Women professionally active- It's me" project concerning: 60h of <u>UE projects management</u> training, 8h of <u>labour legislation</u> training, 30h of <u>computer skills</u> training (MS Office), 8h of <u>labour market</u> training, 8h of <u>psychology</u> workshop, 8h <u>auto presentation</u> skills training, english language course finished with TOEIC exam

#### 2009-2011

French language course at level B2/C1 in Alliance Français Language School in Wrocław (3 semesters)

#### October 2014-July 2015

English language course at A2 level (coursebook A2/B1) with final exam

#### Education

#### 1982-1987

Studies at Faculty of National Economics at Oskar Lange's Academy of Economics (now University of Economics) in Wrocław

### Skills and Interests

#### Languages

#### Interests

- $\circ$  Natural medicine  $\circ$  Sports: fitness and  $\circ$  Films and festivals and herbalism skiing
- Gardening Classical music